<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mercury</string>
    <string name="scanButtonText">Scan QRCode</string>
    <string name="aboutTitle">About Mercury</string>
    <string name="aboutText">
Mercury v%1$s\n\nFor further information, please
visit the homepage.\n\nSome icons used in Mercury have been created by 
Androidicons.com. That work is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution 
3.0 Unported License.\n\nCopyright (c) 2010, Carson Brown, David Barrera and
Mohammad Mannan All rights reserved.\n\nRedistribution and use in source and
binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the
following conditions are met:\n\nRedistributions of source code must retain the
above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this
list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or
other materials provided with the distribution.  Neither the name of Mercury nor
the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived
from this software without specific prior written permission.  THIS SOFTWARE IS
PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT
SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT,
INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR
PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE
OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n\n
	</string>
	<string name="aboutGoToHomepage">Go to homepage</string>
	<string name="aboutClose">Close</string>
	<string name="badScanTitle">Scan Error</string>
	<string name="badScanMessage">Sorry, that was not a valid password QR code to be decrypted, or the input was malformed. Try again?</string>
	<string name="badScanYes">Yes</string>
	<string name="badScanNo">No</string>
	<string name="getBarcodeReaderTitle">Barcode Reader Support</string>
	<string name="getBarcodeReaderMessage">In order to use Mercury, you need to 
install Barcode Scanner. Would you like to be taken to the Android Market to
download it?
	</string>
	<string name="getBarcodeReaderYes">Yes</string>
	<string name="getBarcodeReaderNo">No</string>
	<string name="step1">No key pair found, generate key pair from menu</string>
	<string name="step1_5">Transmit public key or encrypt new password from menu</string>
	<string name="step2">Scan password or encrypt new password from menu</string>
	<string name="step3">Scan retrieved password from mail</string>
	<string name="overWriteKeys">Generating a new keypair will make all 
	previously generated password QR codes unusable. Are you sure you want to do this?</string>
</resources>
